<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>at redradrat&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://redradrat.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on at redradrat&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://redradrat.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://redradrat.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redradrat.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>attr. L. Campostrini, 2019
  Hey there! My name is Ralph Kühnert and I&amp;rsquo;m a Cloud Architect, Software Developer and DevOps Engineer. I design and build elastic, scalable cloud infrastructure to serve highly-available applications on a global scale, using modern, cloud-native and predominantly open-source tech.
I&amp;rsquo;m striving to design generic infrastructure and application platforms, maintained and operated through normalized interfaces. I believe that all componentry should be accessible and exposable via unified and homogenous APIs, enabling globally-distributed teams with different technical backgrounds to interconnect flawlessly through normalized abstraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://redradrat.xyz/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redradrat.xyz/contact/</guid>
      <description>Regarding specific projects, please find the detail on my GitHub.
For other requests, I&amp;rsquo;m available on Keybase: https://keybase.io/redradrat</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://redradrat.xyz/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redradrat.xyz/projects/</guid>
      <description>[active] aws-iam-operator A kubernetes-native controller to control AWS Identity and Access Management. Provides CustomResources to reconcile Policies, Users, Groups and Roles. Developed, to help with AWS abstraction via kubernetes-native interfaces. Currently under development&amp;hellip; can be found on GitHub.
[active] cloud-objects Here I&amp;rsquo;m trying to collect all cloud service abstractions that I&amp;rsquo;m working on as a golang library in a per-instance C(R)UD fashion. This is a spin-off from the aws-iam-operator. Currently under development&amp;hellip; can be found on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>